Guide to the Silicon Valley Ephemera Collection, 1976- M0443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications, Series 1
  - General, Subseries 1.1
    - Innovative Devices, Inc. Business plan, 1987 Jun; undated; 2 items (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Institute for the Future. Miscellaneous documents, 1988 - 1990; 4 items (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - IntelliMatch, Inc. Promotional brochures, 1997; 5 items. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Interaction magazine, 1992 Summer; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Interactive Conference & Expo, 1994; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Interactive Entertainment Merchants Association, 2000 July 19-21; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Interface Age, Inc. Advertisement, 1978; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Interface Age, Inc
    - Interface Group, Inc. Computer Faire materials, 1989-1990; 3 items (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Interface Group, Inc
    - International Business Machines Corporation. Investigation of two Haloid-Xerox machines as new product opportunities in the office reproducing equipment field, 1958 Dec 1; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - International Business Machines Corporation. Papers, 1978; 1981; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Includes annual report, 1978, and product brochure, 1981.
    - International Business Machines Corporation. Papers, 1986; 8 items (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - International Computer Products flyer, circa 1981; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence. Conference packet, 23 Aug 1987; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 11)
      International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence
    - International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence. Conference packet, 1991, 1993; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - International Web Publishing House. Promotional materials, circa 1996; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Internet Expo conference materials, 1993 -1998; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Internet Mall, Inc. Promotional brochure, 1997; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - InterNex Information Services, Inc. Promotional materials, product data and press releases, 1995-1997; 8 items. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Intersil Inc. Annual Report, 1979; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - InterTainment Conference, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Intuit. Product catalog, 1997; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Ithaca Audio. Papers, undated; 4 items (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Ithaca Audio.
    - JavaOne conference materials, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Kelly Data. Promotional flyer, undated; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Kelly Data.
    - Koala Technologies Corporation. Promotional flyer, circa 1987-1988; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - KOEI Corporation. Promotional catalog, 1996; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - L-5 Society. Silicon Valley Chapter. Newsletter, Vol. 7, nos. 7, 8 & 9, 1984 Jul-Sep (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Lam Research Corporation. Annual report, 1995; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Liberty Systems. Product catalog and price list, 1993; 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Lifeboat Assoicates. User's manual and correspondence, 1982-1994; 4 items. (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Gift of P.S.C. Lewis, 1994.
      User's manual and correspondence concerning computer manufactured by Lifeboat Associates, 1982.
      Lewis, P.S.C.
    - Lightspeed Software. Promotional folder, 1993; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - LinkExchange. Promotional flyer, circa 1996; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - ;login:, Vol. 7, no. 1-5, 1982; 5 items (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ;login:, Vol. 8, no. 1-4, Vol. 9., no. 2, 1984; 5 items (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Logitech. Papers, 1986-1987; 1993; 1 folder. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Engelbart, D. C., 1925-2013; Logitech
    - LucasArts. Promotional journal, 1994; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 5)
      THE ADVENTURER promotional journal, no. 7, Winter 1994.
    - MP Computers. Business card and product catalog, circa 1994; 2 items (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Business card of Sendy Wu and product catalog.
    - MacAvenue catalog, undated; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - MacWorld Exposition, 1995; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - MacWorld Exposition, 1986; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - MacWorld. Papers, 1986-1988; 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Marin Computer Center. Papers, undated; 2 items (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Marin Computer Center.
    - Marinchip Systems. Promotional flyer, undated; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Marinchip Systems.
    - MasterLink, Inc. Promotional brochure, circa 1996; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Maximum PC, 1998 Sep; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Maxtor. Promotional pamphlet, 1993; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Promotional pamphlet for Maxtor hard drives.
    - McAfee Associates, Inc. Product catalogs and poster,., 1991-1993; 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Product catalogs, graphic poster detailing anti-virus and personal computer software and a company card.
    - McDonnell Douglas Information Systems Group. Promotional flyer, 1986; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 17)
      McDonnell Douglas Information Systems Group.
    - Media Vision. Product catalog and information brochures, 1993; 11 items. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Micro Systems Development. Product description, undated; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Micro Systems Development.
    - Micro World. Promotional flyer, undated; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 20)
      Micro World.
    - MicroPro International Corporation. Product brochures and promotional flyers, 1987, circa 1990; 4 items (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Includes detailed product information brochure on Wordstar Professional Release 5 word processing program for PCs.
    - Microsoft Corporation. Guide & directory, circa 1987-2000; 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 23)
      Microsoft Word pocket guide plus Microsoft Excel services directory.
    - Microsoft Corporation. Journal entitled One-to-One with Microsoft, promotional pamphlets and catalogs [1 of 2], 1987-1996; 23 items (Box 12, Folder 24)
      Journal entitled One-to-One with Microsoft, Winter 1987, promotional pamphlets and catalogs; WINDOWS 95 FOR DUMMIES book; Windows 95 CD-ROM demo; Windows 95 newspaper advertisement; SHOW DIRECTORY, WINDOWS SOLUTIONS CONFERENCE & EXPOSTION, September, 1994.
    - Microsoft Corporation. Journal entitled One-to-One with Microsoft, promotional pamphlets and catalogs [2 of 2], 1987-1996; 23 items (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - MacUser, 1997; 5 items. (Box 13)
      Includes 5 issues of MacUser magazine, 1997 Apr., July, Aug., Sept., & Oct.
    - MacWorld, 1997 - 1998; 7 items. (Box 13)
      Includes 7 issues of MacWorld magazine, 1997 July, Aug., Sept., Oct., Dec., 1998 Jan., Feb.
    - Filevision Magazine, Issue no. 1, 1984 Winter; 2 items. (Box 13)
    - Interaction, Fall 1991, Fall 1992, Winter 1992, Holiday Issue 1993; 4 items (Box 13)
    - Microsoft Corporation. Windows shopping: a catalog of products for Microsoft Windows, undated; 1 v. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Microsoft Internet User & Developer conference, 1997; 1 item (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Midwest Affiliation of Computer Clubs. Computerfest: announcement, 1978; 1 item (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Computerfest Midwest Affiliation of Computer Clubs
    - Mindscape (Firm). Product catalogs, 1992-1997; 6 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - MindSource Software Engineers. Promotional pamphlet, 1996; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - MIPS Technologies, Inc. Promotional pamphlet, 1993; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Promotional pamphlet for the MIPS R4000 microprocessor.
    - The Portable Companion. -- Osborne Computer Corporation, 1982; 1 volume (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Premier issue of THE PORTABLE COMPANION journal. Depicts the portable Osborne 1 surrounded by Afghan rebels and being used by THE CHICAGO SUN-TIMES journalist David Kline to file his articles on the Afghanistan conflict. June/July, 1982.
      Kline, David
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1992-1995; 10 items (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Mitch Hall Associates. Promotional brochures for MACWORLD Exposition, 1987-2000; 2 items (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Transfer, 1998-2001
      Promotional brochure published in 1987 for MACWORLD Exposition at the Moscone Center in San Francisco, January 15-17, 1988.
      Macworld Expo, San Francisco, CA, 2000; MACWORLD Exposition, San Francisco, CA, 1988.; World Expo Co.; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Monotype Typography, Inc. Product catalogs, 1993-1994; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Typeface catalogs.
    - Morgan Kaufmann Publishers, Inc. Catalogs, circa 1988; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Morrow Computers. A guide to products and services, 1985; 2 items (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Morrow Design. Microdesign user's manual, undated; 1 v. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Morrow Design. MDT20 Terminal reference manual, 1983; 1 v. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Multimedia Expo conference guides, 1993 -1995; 3 items (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Multimedia Live! conference materials, 1995; 1 item (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - NASA Ames Research Center. Ames Research Center zero base report from a May 1974 survey, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - NASA Ames Research Center. NASA/Ames Research Facilities Summary, 1974; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - NASA Ames Research Center. Promotional brochure, circa 1996; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Promotional brochure on information technology at NASA.
    - Microsystems magazine, 1981 - 1983; 13 items (Box 15)
      Includes 13 issues of Microsystems magazine, Vol. 2, no. 4-6 (1981), Vol. 4, no. 2 -4, 6, 7 (2 copies), 8-10, 12
    - Morrow Owner's Review, Vol. 1, no. 1 - Vol. 1, no. 3, 1984; 4 items (Box 15)
    - Silicon Valley Magazine, 1982; 1 v. (Box 16)
      Journal entitled SILICON VALLEY MAGAZINE, July 1982.
    - Silicon Valley Engineer, Vol. 1, no. 1, Vol. 2, no. 1-4, 1989 - 1990 (Box 16)
    - Morrow Owner's Review, Vol. 1, no. 4 - Vol. 4, no. 6, 1984 - 1988; 23 items (Box 16)
    - O'Reilly & Associates, Inc. Guides, product catalogs and promotional flyers, 1993-1997; 11 items. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Guides, product catalogs and promotional flyers, including the Summer 1993 issue of ORA.COM magazine.
    - Objectivity, Inc. Promotional flyer, 1997; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Octel Communications Corporation. Octel Solution Alliance Member Reference List, 1997; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - On Line. Newsletter, 1978; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 4)
      On Line
    - One/D. Product announcement, 1986; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      One/D
    - Online toys, 2000; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - OnMoney.com mailer, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Optibase, Inc. Pamphlet promoting MPEG Showsite software, 1998; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Oracle Corporation. Promotional invitation, 1997; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Invitation to join the Oracle Developer Programme.
    - Orion Instruments. Promotional flyer, circa 1986; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Orion Instruments
    - Osborne & Associates, Inc. Catalog and photographs, 1978-1982; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Osborne & Associates, Inc.
    - Otto Electronics. Promotional flyer, undated; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 12)
      Otto Electronics.
    - Pacific Studies Center. Global Electronics, 1985; 3 v. (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Formerly the Global Electronics Information Newsletter. Global Electronics newsletter, n. 52, April 1985, n. 53, May 1985, n. 54, June 1985.
    - Pacific Studies Center. Silicon Valley: Paradise or Paradox?, 1977; 1 v. (Box 18, Folder 14)
      Pamphlet entitled SILICON VALLEY: PARADISE OR PARADOX? THE IMPACT OF HIGH TECHNOLOGY INDUSTRY ON SANTA CLARA COUNTY. Pamphlet prepared by Alan Bernstein, Bob DeGrasse, Rachael Grossman, Chris Paine and Lenny Siegel
    - Parsec Research, Inc., 1 v. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - PC Consumer, 1984 Mar; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - PC Tech Forum seminar. Microprocessors for the PDA's set-tops, and video games / Jim Turley, 1996; 1 v. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - PC Tech Forum seminar. Understanding the changing PC market / Dave Tremblay, Matt Sargent, Aaron Goldberg, Peter Glaskowsky, 1996; 1 v. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Periodical Guide for Computerists: order form, 1978; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Peripherals, Etc., 1983; 1 v. (96 p.) (Box 18, Folder 20)
      Peripherals, Etc.
    - Personal TEX, Inc. Product catalog, Spring 1986; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
      Personal TEX, Inc.
    - Pixar. Promotional postcards and flyer, circa 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Plotkin, Hal. SDI and Silicon Valley: betting on a system experts say can't work, 1986 Oct 29; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 23)
      News article written for Metro: Santa Clara Valley's Weekly.
      Metro;; Plotkin, Hal
    - PolyMorphic Systems. Product information, undated; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 24)
      PolyMorphic Systems.
    - Polywell Computers, Inc. Promotional pamphlets, circa 1993; 2 items (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Promotional pamphlets detailing a product line of home computers.
    - Portable Computer. -- Miller Freeman Publications, 1983; 2 v. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      PORTABLE COMPUTER journal, including the premier issue, February/March 1983 and the August 1983 issue.
    - PPC ROM Project. User's manual, 1981; 1 item (Box 19, Folder 3)
      PC ROM Project; Hewlett-Packard Company
    - Precision Data, Inc. Promotional pamphlet, circa 1978; 2 items (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Promotional pamphlet detailing activities of the company.
    - Precision Image Corporation. Product announcement, 1986; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Precision Image Corporation.
    - Precision Instrument Company. Annual reports, 1962 - 1963; 1965 - 1967; 5 items. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Precision Instrument Company. Annual reports, 1966 - 1969; 4 items. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Precision Instrument Company. Annual reports, 1970 - 1971; 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Premiere Technologies, Inc. / Netcom Orchestrate. Promotional flyers, 1998; 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Prodigy. Promotional pamphlet, 1991; 1 item (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Promotional pamphlet for Prodigy internet service.
    - Productivity Software Center. Productivity Software Review, 1986; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 11)
      Brown Bag Software.; Productivity Software Center.
    - Publish. -- Integrated Media, Inc., 1993; 1 v. (Box 19, Folder 12)
      Journal entitled PUBLISH: THE ART AND TECHNOLOGY OF ELECTRONIC PUBLISHING, November, 1993.
    - Publishing Technology Management, Inc. The Gilbane Report, 1993; 2 items (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Journal entitled THE GILBANE REPORT ON OPEN INFORMATION & DOCUMENT SYSTEMS, v. 1, no. 4, September 1993, and a reprint from v. 1, no. 1, March 1993.
    - Pulse Entertainment. Promotional mailer, 1996; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 14)
      Promotional mailer for Bad Mojo: The Roach Game.
    - Radio Shack. Product information, undated; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 15)
      Radio Shack.
    - Radius, Inc. Promotional pamphlet and product announcement, 1987; 1993; 1 item (Box 19, Folder 16)
      Promotional pamphlet detailing services offered to Radius customers.
      Radius, Inc; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Raya Systems, Inc. Promotional mailing, 1993; 4 items. (Box 19, Folder 17)
      Promotional mailing containing information on The AIDS Avenger! computer game. Includes an introductory letter from sales coordinator Beth Gemeny.
      Gemeny, Beth.; The AIDS Avenger!
    - Raytheon Semiconductor. Linear IC's, 1976; 1 v. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Real Conference 2000, San Jose Convention Center, San Jose, 2000 May 22-26; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Red Herring. -- [S.l.]: Flipside Communications, Inc., 1994; 1 v. (Box 19, Folder 20)
      Journal entitled THE RED HERRING: THE TECHNOLOGY STRATEGIC & FINANCIAL MONTHLY, January 1994.
    - Relia Technologies. Promotional flyer for 4-user internet hub, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Santa Clara County: past present, 1985; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rich's Business guide to Santa Clara County's Silicon Valley. -- Los Altos, Calif.: Business Directories, Inc., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - ROLM Corporation. Annual reports, 1980; 2 items (Box 20, Folder 3)
      2 copies of the 1980 annual report.
    - RW Products and Sales. Product information, undated; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 4)
      RW Products and Sales.
    - SalesKit Software. Promotional postcard, circa 1990; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Art Institute. Art in the age of electronic media, 1993 Oct 21-23 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Focus Magazine. Chip Chat, 1983 Fall; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 7)
      San Jose City College.
    - San Jose City College. Computer technology: program of studies, undated; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - San Jose Mercury News. Millenium series on Silicon Valley life, 1999; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Santa Clara County (Calif.). Planning Dept. Industrial Land Needs. Part 1: Summary, 1965; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Santa Clara Systems, Inc. Product announcements, 1986; 7 items. (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Santa Clara Systems, Inc.
    - Second International Conference on Supercomputing. Promotional flyer,., 1987; 2 items (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Security Pacific National Bank. Northern Coastal California; Economic Trends in the Seventies, 1977; 1 v. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Semicon. Flyer, 1987; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Semicon
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute. Product announcement, 1987-1988; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute. SEMI membership directory, 1983 - 1984; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Semiconductor Research Corporation. Graphics for oral presentation, 1984 Oct 8; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 18)
      Semiconductor Research Corporation; ACM conference; Cavin, Ralph K. III
    - Server Technology Inc. Promotional pamphlet and flyers, 1995-1996; 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Seybold San Francisco conference materials, 1993 Oct (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Seybold San Francisco conference materials, 1994 Mar 13-14 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Seybold San Francisco conference materials, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seybold San Francisco conference materials, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Seybold San Francisco conference materials, 1999 Aug 30-Sep 3; 2 items (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Seybold. Windows solutions conference packet, 1993; 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Sierra On-Line. Product catalogs, issue of journal entitled Sierra On-Line News, 1991-1996; 8 items (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Product catalogs, journal entitled SIERRA ON-LINE E-NEWS, Issue 2, June 1996.
    - Silicon Graphics Computer Systems. Papers, circa 1987; 1 folder (includes 1 video cassette). (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Silicon Graphics Computer Systems.
    - Silicon Graphics Computer Systems. Annual report, 1995; 1 item (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Silicon Graphics Computer Systems. Promotional pamphlets, prinout of announcement of the formation of a new Silicon Graphics moderated email list, printout of Iris On-Line, issue of Iris Universe, 1993-1996; 7 items (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Promotional pamphlets, printout of announcement of the formation of a new Silicon Graphics moderated email list, July 1993, printout of journal entitled IRIS ON-LINE, v. 1, issue 4, August 1, 1993, issue of journal entitled IRIS UNIVERSE: THE MAGAZINE OF VISUAL COMPUTING, no. 24, Spring, 1993.
    - Silicon Valley Entrepreneurs' Conference brochure, 1999 May 6; 1 item (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Project application, 1985 - 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Project application, 1986 - 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Quarterly report, 1985 Oct-Dec (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Inc. San Carlos (Calif.) laboratory register listing visitor names and company affiliations, 1939-1966; 4 items (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Gift of William T. Cooke.
      Register lists visitor names and company affiliations, June 1939 to November 1940. Includes a later page of Garden Notes from 1962, and accounts for a house at 242 Forest St., Oberlin, Ohio, from 1965-1966. Folder includes 3 letters concerning the donation of this item to Stanford. Added author: Cooke, William T.
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Quarterly report, 1986 Jan-Mar (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Quarterly report, 1986 Apr-Jun (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Spotlight: an executive conference: materials, 1995 July (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - SRI International. Papers, 1965-1985; 1 folder. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      SRI International
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Quarterly report, 1986 Jul-Sep (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Quarterly report, 1987 Jan-Mar (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Final summary report, 1985 Oct 1-1987 Sep 30; 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Silicon Valley Information Center. Tomorrow magazine and promotional pamphlet, 1986; 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Silicon Valley Research Group, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Siltec Corporation. Annual report, 1978; 1 item (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Softletter, 1994; 1 v. (Box 22, Folder 10)
      Newsletter entitled SOFTLETTER: TRENDS AND STRATEGIES IN SOFTWARE PUBLISHING, v. 10, no. 19, February 8, 1994.
    - SoftQuad, Inc. Registration form, circa 1990; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Registration form for SoftQuad's "Getting Started with SGML"
    - Softsync, Inc. Product announcement, 1986; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Softsync, Inc.
    - Software.com, Inc. Promotional pamphlet, 1996; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Software Publishers Assoc. Spring symposium. List of attendees, 1994; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Software Tools Communications, Vol. 1, no. 1-2; Vol. 2, no. 1; no. 4-7, 1979 - 1980; 1 v. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Software Tools Users Group, 1982; 3 items (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Spa: invitation to opening ceremonies, 1994; 1 item (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Action for Nuclear Disarmament, undated; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Macintosh User's Group (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University. Graduate School of Business. Softbank Venture capital internet portfolio directory, 2000 Apr; 1 v. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University. Office of Technology Licensing brochure, undated; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Xerox Corporation.; Dessauer, John H.
    - STARCOM Electronics, Inc. Promotional flyer with client list, circa 1995; 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Stereographics Corp. Preliminary business plan, 1985 Nov 11 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Strategic Business Services. Computer stores and the sale of small business computers, 1979 Jan; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Business Services. A strategic analysis of the IBM 4300 series, 1979 Nov; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Business Services. IBM, ATT, and ROLM switching systems, Vol. 1, 1980 Apr; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Strategic Business Services. Impact of the interconnected offices, 1979 June; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Strategic Business Services. Laser printers, 1979; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Business Services. Wang's integrated information strategy: successes and problems, 1980 April; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Simulations, Inc. Catalogs, 1987 - 1988; 2 items (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Sun Microsystems, Inc. Catalysts: a catalog of third party software and hardware from Sun Microsystems, 1987 Winter; 1 v. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Sunshine Power Company.
    - Sun Microsystems, Inc. Invitations to Sun booth at Usenix conference, San Francisco, Calif. and to Sun seminar demonstrating Sun products, undated; 2 items (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Sun Microsystems, Inc. Promotional brochures, 1987; 3 items (Box 24, Folder 6)